Write these two stories and we will get
into the other ones.
Drop carrier page, right?
This is a new UI that we will need for
tender page.
You go to the tender page and tell you
where it is required.
If I select this tender and then you see
the tender list,
this is the tender list and different
tabs. Underneath this tender list,
we'll need a drop carrier list.
So what it actually means is drop carrier.
When the system is generating this list,
there are certain qualifications, right?
You need to have a pickup.
date and delivery date,
you will need certain other information
in order to qualify to make it to this
list on the top.
There are, there were some.
carriers that were eligible for this
particular shipment,
but did not make the first cut of the
list, right?
They didn't meet certain qualifications.
So we wanted to give those carriers,
which did not meet the qualifications,
a separate list called the drop carrier
list.
Right, so that will be,
we want to keep it below this particular
list.
It will have very similar kind of field.
I'm going to give you all the field
information on all those.
The idea is this is the tendering list
and below that you will have a drop
carrier list. Make sense so far?
Yeah, Maxim, yeah,
but there are so many carriers on this
Right.
second list.
Yeah, that is where we get, yeah,
this is the first list,
How many?
but the second list we can have two,
can have one,
it is going to be based on routing,
what the routing had returned.
Alright.
It evaluated 10 carriers, right?
Out of that, only four qualified.
There could be 6 in the drop carrier list.
So they did not meet the requirements.
Go ahead.
Okay,
so that will be handled by the system.
But what is required is, if certain,
if you look here in the payload,
let me see if I have that.
I kept it open up here.
If you see the payload that is going to
come from.
Routing, this is the routing.
So if you see here,
this is the option one, right?
So this is the first carrier.
The first carrier,
and it has the parameters related to this
first carrier, time, date,
date it is not present here,
but they're going to add it.
But it has cost, it has distance,
distance that is it is, then transit days.
Could you?
I'm sorry, Janardhana,
could you copy that copy to me that
payload, please? That will be helpful.
Yes, the whole payload, it's fine.
I.
This one? Sure. Yeah.
Okay.
There's a sample payload, OK?
Thanks.
Okay, so if you see this,
this is a usable carrier list.
You see here, it says usable carriers.
And below, after this,
Huh?
it says drop carrier list.
So it did not meet the usable condition.
So there are certain carriers which
dropped out of this main list.
So the usable carrier list is what is
this?
Right?
They can tender everything is kind of
ready and it can be tendered to evaluated.
But there are some carriers which did not
make to this list, usable carrier list.
That's called the drop carrier list.
Right? It could be whatever reason.
It says the reason, right? Prohibited.
This carrier is prohibited.
This carrier has no rates found.
So it cannot make the list.
Then you can see missing transit times.
So because of that,
it did not make the list.
Then many other reasons, right?
It could be so many numerous reasons.
So it's going to return the reasons and
it's going to return the details.
And that is why,
because it did not meet certain
conditions.
Huh.
fell into the drop carriers. So far clear.
Yeah.
Okay, so in TMS also has the same.
So you have seen this page.
So these are all lists of shipments.
If I go here, if I go to equipments.
Okay, so you see one carrier here,
only one carrier is available, right?
And then if you come down, okay,
this doesn't have a drop carrier.
Maybe I have to pick a...
Lost.
Okay,
so you see here there is only one carrier
and also there is a drop carrier button
enabled, right? So if you click on this,
you can see that RLCA,
only one carrier is part of this drop
carrier list.
So it means that two carriers qualified,
Mhm.
one carrier.
Two carriers were selected initially.
One carrier got selected as a usable list.
The other carrier dropped because missing
transit time.
Right, so if you go here, it did not,
it had a delivery date,
but it could not calculate the pickup
date because it did not have a transit
type.
Makes sense.
If you know the transit time as two days,
you already know the delivery date,
Mhm.
Yep.
but you can calculate the pickup date.
Since the transit time was not available,
it could not calculate the pickup date,
and that is why it dropped out of the
And.
list.
No, OK.
Okay.
Right, so that is what it says,
the reason.
So...
So, that that that is automatic.
Francis, yeah, go ahead, go ahead.
Automatic. We don't have to do anything.
Oh, I see. Yeah, okay.
The routing list is going to give you
that information, right? Whenever the,
Sadick.
Uh-huh.
you know, this particular detail, right?
Huh?
Here there is going to be a call to the
routing, right?
When the shipment is created,
there is a call to the routing service.
So when a call is made,
it is going to return this list.
Okay, it's fine.
Makes sense? Yeah, okay. Okay,
so now so far we have created,
we want to create this particular list,
exact list, right? In the volume, sorry,
in the...
This one.
Is that?
Here, just below in TMS,
it has a separate screen.
You want to just provide it below the
screen itself,
and we will have to say day.
Drop carrier,
you have to have it as some kind of an
idea, right? So it should be collapsible,
click, it should open,
then it should give you all the entire
list, right? Drop carrier,
so that the user can see and see the list,
first of all. Make sense?
The.
Okay, if I go to the story,
the display drop carrier,
Yeah.
Mhm.
what are all the fields?
I've given you fields and examples, right?
So it's CAC, carrier name, equipment,
pickup date and time,
delivery date and time, date, start date,
stop date, then transit time.
I've given all these explanation.
For is more for developers to understand,
but these are like what information needs
to be populated, right? All these fields.
OK, if you see here.
There's another tab called Volume
Commitment, right?
I want to move this to a separate story.
Right?
Because Dave needs to give me some rules
behind it,
how to calculate what needs to be done.
Yes.
So what he said was that is very
difficult.
There is a lot of codes in a coordinate
and I need to look into it.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to
move this to a separate story, right?
Yeah.
Once I move it,
so you will have two information here.
One is the details about the carrier,
and these are also volume commitment is
also about details about the carrier,
but this is not finalized, so.
You don't have to work on this one right
now, right?
You can just leave it as it is.
Right,
so you just work on this particular list.
Make sense? Or even if you want,
you can just put the fields and just keep
it right,
whatever information what we have.
But the idea behind volume commitment is
for this particular carrier,
what is my weekly volume of trucks that
they are going to give?
So here I have it as commitment, right?
So commitment is it'll going to give you
a number and then it'll go to give you an
UOM.
UOM is 10 loads per week or it could be
10 kgs per day, right? Or 10,
000 kgs per day.
It could be what combination it could be,
right? That is going to be a commitment.
Commitment means it is like carrier is.
agreed to do 10 loads per week.
Right,
and how many they have accepted so far
Mhm.
Bye.
for this week?
How many they have accepted? So,
they have accepted 6 loads.
This will be calculated as a commitment
utilization, right?
And open is remaining commitment capacity.
Say, if they are if they have...
accepted 6 loads, what is remaining?
10 minus 6, which is 4.
Right? Comments.
If there are any comments for this
particular carrier,
carrier commitment notes.
So if they have provided any carrier
commitment notes,
they will provide it here.
And this is CVC ID, right?
CVC ID is nothing but you will see it
here.
CBC ID, right?
This is the rule for this particular rule
number. This is the rule number,
kind of like...
How do you say?
This is the volume commitment code in the
master table, right?
This is rule number one.
For this rule number one,
for this particular carrier and the
equipment,
the carrier is committed for 10 loads.
For a different equipment,
they might have committed a different
number of loads, right?
That is why this rule is important.
What we will do with this rule is we will
take this rule and calculate what are all
the carriers,
what are all the specific carrier and
accepted the loads for this particular
rule so that we can arrive at this number.
All right.
Hope it makes sense, right?
So this is like we are trying to capture
this.
So it means that every line item will
have its own rule.
It is not like this rule is applicable
for the entire list.
Every SCAC will have its own CVC ID,
right?
So that is why I have CVC ID as one of
the information in the list, right?
But here you would see it as if like it
is applicable for the entire list.
entire drop carrier list,
but it is actually applicable for each
and every option of the drop carrier list.
Okay,
so each carrier will have its own rule.
It's.
That's what it means.
And this rule is useful for Odyssey 1 to
evaluate how many loads or shipments this
particular carrier has accepted for this
equipment for that particular.
Pick up date or week?
Right? So yeah, again,
this might not be helpful for you,
but I'm just giving you as an idea, right,
how it works. Okay.
Yeah.
Right, so we need these two details.
So I will move this.
You just maybe just plug this information
as part of the design, then it could,
you know,
we might need some refinement on this
particular logic.
I think it's more the logic refinement,
not the display refinement. Okay.
So this is what it is.
So now I'll go to the next section where..
.
We have a carrier and we would want to
move this carrier from a drop carrier
list to the usable carrier list.
Usable carrier is,
I want to move the carrier from here to
here.
Make sense?
I want to take this carrier and move it
Yeah.
here, right? I want to use it.
How can I use it?
So I would select this carrier.
And then process CAC.
Okay.
So once I process SCAC, it is saying,
SCAC, what is the equipment,
what is the pickup date,
what is the time zone, right?
What is delivery date and time zone? Here,
TMS is automatically calculating
something, right? It says again,
could not calculate the cost of.
RLCA missing the transit time could not
calculate ETA, right? Ideally,
Yeah.
what it should do is...
if the dates are not available.
In this case, the dates are not available.
Right, they.
Lego.
In this case, the dates are not available.
The delivery date is only available.
The pickup date is not available, right?
Once it processes the SCAC,
it should ask the force the user to fill
the date.
Right? It should force in Odyssey one,
that is what we are trying to do,
force the user to fill the date.
Once they click on OK, right,
it would call the routing,
it would call the rating.
Right, could not rate.
It is going to display the message saying
could not rate. OK,
and then this carrier got added here.
You see that?
Yeah.
Right, so now it did not calculate a rate,
it displayed a message,
say here it is blank,
saying rate does not calculate, right?
So there is no cost here.
And then you see it added a pickup date
and a delivery date.
But this is what we are going to force
the user to give a date.
Right?
And then it could not calculate the
transit time.
So you don't have to be worried about all
this, right?
So if there is a transit time it can
provide as calling from routing,
it will provide a transit time.
But it was able to calculate the distance.
It did provide the distance.
Right,
then it told about the communication
method,
how you have to notify this particular
carrier.
Right, this is not important for us.
So what is the distance source?
So whatever it is possible,
it is going to bring all that information
back during a routing or a rating call.
Right,
and it's going to fill the other details
here.
Makes sense.
Okay, let me go to the story.
Mm.
This is what I have detailed here, right?
This is the tender tab process CAC, right?
How do you process CAC?
There are two ways to process CAC.
We saw from drop carrier list and the
other one is you will see here process
CAC, right?
I can select a carrier from this list.
And I can pick any carrier.
Let's just add.
And then I can select the equipment.
It will tell me what is the relevant
equipment for this CAC.
I'll put it as tank truck and then add.
Once I add,
it is saying select the pickup date and
the delivery date,
just like how it asked for select pickup
date and delivery date, right?
I'm not going to do anything,
but in Odyssey One,
it will force the user to pick a date,
right? If I do that.
Okay,
just trying to call the rating and then
it did add, right?
So it was not able to identify what is
the cost for this particular carrier.
Then it did automatically give a date
because it did get some transit time,
right? Because using that,
it calculated some details.
So then it got added.
The process followed right from a drop
carrier list and the process SCAC,
adding SCAC and the equipment from here,
both are same. Steps are the same.
But in the drop carrier list,
it is returned by routing. Here,
the user is going and adding it.
Makes sense so far?
They can pick any carrier,
it doesn't matter.
Yeah.
Okay, okay, now we'll go to the story.
Right, so process CAC action,
the process CAC shall only be available
to carrier displayed within the drop
carrier section, right?
So it says about this.
So if you, one more thing, right?
If you select the same carrier and say
process SCAC,
it is going to say carrier and equipment
combination,
RLCA and LTL already exist in the list,
right? So we added this before,
it is going to give a warning message.
So that also needs to be covered.
I have written all those thing in the
story.
I'm just giving you all the high-level
information so that you can design
accordingly.
Okay,
the process CAC shall only be available
for carry as displayed within the dropped
carrier section.
Only one SCAC can be processed at a time.
While processing is in progress,
process CAC shall be disabled.
So it means that the button should not be
enabled for second carrier processing.
Right,
process CAC shall be disabled and
additional user clicks shall not be
allowed.
Now routing processing.
Once user clicks on process SCAC action
under the drop carrier,
the routing call is attempted for this
SCAC. That is what we said, right?
Whenever you select a date,
then it automatically goes and calls the
routing.
When the routing is successful,
when routing completes successfully,
pickup and delivery date available,
carrier information shall be copied from
the drop carrier section into the tender
list.
The routing results shall be refreshed
for the carrier copied message.
That should be a message to the user
saying that routing completed
successfully,
and then this message will be there for
three seconds and it will disappear,
right? In case where the routing failed,
routing failed is, you processed SCAC.
You go to this one, drop carrier.
I select the carrier.
If I say press process CAC,
it is calling the routing service, right?
When it is calling the routing service,
it is trying to calculate the date for
the carrier.
If it is not able to calculate the date,
it would ask the user to fill a date,
right? That is what I am calling as.
A routing failure. If I go back here,
what is routing failure?
If routing call fails,
if the routing call did not return dates,
right?
Dialog box to get user to fill in the
date.
Look at the manual pickup and delivery
date entry, right? I've written here,
what is the manual?
manual pickup and delivery entry.
This is the dialog box we saw there,
where the user will have to select a date,
and once they select the date,
then they have to click OK to do it.
So here,
the user will have to manually select a
pickup and a delivery date.
Right, then it is OK,
then the rating service is called behind
the scene,
once you have a pickup and the delivery
date. OK, while calling the rating,
if the rating failed.
Information dialogue reminding the user
they should get a quote, right?
So if they say they were able to give a
date,
but it is possible that the rating failed.
Rating failed means it did not return a
rate, right?
We did see here what it means by saying
it did not return a rate.
Eight.
If you go here, it did not return a rate,
right? These are blank.
So what it should do is it should remind
the user,
it should tell a message to the user
saying that, oh, hey,
you need to fill a quote.
How do you fill a quote? You go here,
go to the quote tab,
and then enter a quote.
I have covered this as part of the other
story.
quote entry story, right?
So I'm just telling you so that it's all
Hey.
gets connected.
So you can enter a quote and you can fill
it. We also have that option in.
Here, right here, or add a quote, right?
This add a quote ideally should be part
Huh.
of this list, right?
Instead of being on the top,
it should be here as part of the dropdown.
Add a quote,
because quote is being added for every
option. It is not added for this.
Uh-huh.
entirely tender, right?
So it is not like add a quote,
it should be add a quote here.
So it should be part of the action on the
side, right? Similarly,
process cat should not be like here in
the drop carrier list,
and you have a drop carrier list.
Each drop carrier list option should have
this action button.
where they would select and process the
stack instead of just having one button
on the top to say like process CAC,
we should have for every option which is
dropped to process the SCAC from here to
the usable list. Make sense?
Uh, I have a question.
Yeah.
So if we have an ad quote into that
dropdown,
that means we can have two quotes because
you can edit a quote, right?
Yeah, you can edit a code, correct.
Edit a rate returned. Say for example,
right? In this case,
I have a rate that has been returned.
I can override this.
I know.
Right.
Yeah,
that you can override with add a quote.
But it's not that is not the same as edit
code.
It is not a quote, right?
You are only adding a quote right now.
You are correcting a rate.
I go here and let me show you.
Yeah,
because the carriers are the ones that
are quoting, right?
You're just editing the rate of something,
right?
See here, here all these are.
not marked, right? Carrier quoted, right?
If I select this carrier and go and enter
a quote.
New coat, OK.
There it was 1400, right?
Now I want to change the base rate as
1000.
Charge, I'll put some charge.
Is it not coming?
So my total value of this quote is 1100,
right?
Now I go and finish coat.
Yeah.
If you see in this particular thing.
From 1400, it got changed to 1100,
and now it changed as carrier quoted.
Right,
you can again go and enter the code and
change it. Edit code.
You can do something to that code,
Change.
then it'll be an edit code.
But you cannot add a quote after you have
one. That's my question. You cannot add,
Make.
What do you mean?
for example,
you added a quote there for Sayon Motor.
Yeah, that was a rate. It initially, yeah,
initially it was a rate returned by the
Yeah, of course.
routing call. I did not like that rate,
so I went and added a quote on behalf of
Mhm.
the carrier.
Now, can you add a quote again or not?
Yeah, that is what edit code, right?
You go to the code, now you have this 1,
100, I can change it, right?
Okay, that's what I was saying.
So add a quote and edit quote is kind of
the same thing, like because they cannot.
They are not different, I mean.
Yeah, they are not different.
You're just overriding it.
The name is called edit code after you
once add a code.
Yeah, okay. Got it.
Right? Yeah, okay.
So I have it as part of this story, right?
So that is what this story is about,
quote entry page, right? Save quote,
Yeah.
edit quote, calculation, and delete quote,
right? That is what I have been covering.
Yeah.
So in this case, you can add a quote,
edit a quote, and delete a quote.
Here,
they have it delete a quote as like edit
and then go make it 0 and make that quote,
right? That is how they do it.
But instead of the user doesn't want like
the number,
they can go and remove the quote.
I'm just giving that option.
Uh-huh.
Right? So here, if you again see here,
it is not quoted.
You can do the same step. Go here,
add a quote, right? New quote,
you can fill out this and $100,
let me see.
Dollars.
Care.
Finalize.
So then you will have 100 here, right?
So now this I have added,
so immediately it does check the box here,
right? So what it is trying to say,
going back to the rating, right? So here,
if the routing call did not return date,
okay,
you will have a dialog box to manually
pick a date, and then it calls the rating.
But if the rating is successful,
that's fine, you will have a rate.
But if the rating failed,
it means that it did not return a rate.
Information dialog box reminding the user
that they should get a quote.
So that is what it is trying to say.
So if did not return a rate,
so this became empty while calling the
rating service.
A message should appear on the screen to
the user saying that, hey,
you need to fill a code for this one
because the rating did not return a rate.
Make sense?
Yep.
Okay,
because rating did not return a rate,
right?
Yeah.
Because when you actually move a carrier,
right,
you move a carrier from drop carrier list
to the main list,
it is calling the routing and the rating.
Right?
Two steps are happening behind the scene.
You are not doing anything from the front
end, but in the back,
it is already calling the routing service.
It is calling the rating service. Right?
The routing was successful.
It was able to find a date,
but could not calculate the rate because
the rate was not available or what could
be the reason? I don't know.
Any reason that could be, right?
It should prompt the user, hey,
I did get the routing, right?
Because your dates are good,
but the rating failed.
So you need to fill a code for it because
you should not leave it empty.
That's the reminder.
That's all I'm trying to say. Make sense?
No.
And what is that code about? About? Ah,
the quotes you say, not quote, right?
Okay.
Add a quote.
A quote, okay, okay, yeah,
similar words looks looks very similar.
Yeah, add a quote.
Okay, it's fine. Got it.
Yeah, add a quote. Yeah,
you should get a quote, right?
That's all it says. Okay.
add carrier to the list at the end of the
set of carriers for that equipment.
So what it is going to do,
if you see here, it is LTL, right?
Say for example, let me add.
LTL, right? If I add a carrier,
what it actually does,
if you watch it very carefully, yeah, yes,
Sanya.
LTL. So if I add this carrier,
what it is going to do is it is going to
insert this carrier between R&
L carrier and what is that?
Chemical Express, right?
So it is going to insert between these
two carriers, right? You watch it.
It says carrier and equipment combination
already in this list, ohh,
already in this list, so OK, only.
Phil.
Okay.
Okay, again,
it's popping the same message. Say,
pickup date and delivery date could not
calculate the cost for ODFL.
Missing transit time could not calculate
the ETA. Okay.
Chip gate is outside the normal range.
It is going to give all these messages
and is going to insert it.
Okay.
But not rate shipments.
Right? So you see here,
it inserted between these two, R&
L and chemical, right?
Because it is going to be based on the
equipment. If the equipment is LTL,
it should insert it towards the end of
that particular equipment,
last line of that equipment, right? If I,
R.
So,
that means the equipment is affecting
if it is...
affecting more in the ranking than...
Anything else, right?
Correct. If you start with LTL,
then it goes TL,
and then it goes tank truck,
and you are adding LTL,
And.
it should put this LTL,
it should find that, okay, this is an LTL,
it should insert that LTL towards the end
of that list. Make sense?
That is what is written in the story.
Add the carrier to the list at the end of
the set of carriers for that equipment.
Make sense?
This is a set of equipment.
And does.
Set of the carriers for that equipment,
correct?
OK.
Right,
it should insert it towards the end of
that list. If I do one more, right,
what is the other carrier?
Uh, CTNS, CTNS.
Okay.
Ideal.
So it is going to go between Old Damian
and Chemical Express. OK,
because it is going to look for.
OK, so.
Just my question again.
I know that you want to bring,
you want to show based on equipment,
all of them grouped, right?
You want to group them based on equipment.
What if,
Exactly.
Yeah.
but that is affecting the ranking as well,
because the ranking is part of the
tendering.
process.
So that means carriers prefer LTL, always,
something like that.
Yeah,
say this is the logic you need to 1st
because for this shipment,
because it has the routing has already
evaluated,
your best carrier selection will come
from LTL, right? If there is no option,
you will go for the TL.
Makes sense.
Do you have the the list of of?
Uh, how can I say this?
No, no, you cannot define it.
It is going to be based on the routing.
I cannot give you a list.
It's all going to evaluate based on the
shipment, shipment information itself.
Say for example, it's only 685 pounds,
right? Ideally, LTL would do.
You don't have to go for TL.
It is more like a one package, right?
It is a small pallet which you are
Ohh.
shipping.
You don't need a truckload for this,
Mhm.
right? So yeah,
say ideally you don't have to use it,
Yeah.
doesn't have to think through all that,
right? When the routing is making a call,
it is going to sort the list and put it
accordingly.
That is why when the user is adding,
it is inserting towards the last in that
particular equipment list.
Okay, when the user is adding manually,
right?
Yeah,
only when user is annually adding or
processing a stack from the drop carrier
list.
Right.
Makes sense.
Okay, but one more question, I mean,
repeating that question.
Do you have the fallback of this list?
Like you say, for example, LTL is first,
right? LTL always is first, then TL,
right? Then IS.
Not like that.
See, not like that.
That is why I'm saying it is for this
No.
particular list. In this case,
LTL is the first.
Because it was the first one initially.
Okay. Yeah, of course,
Correct, initially.
You?
because carriers always like to have
compatible equipments, right? First,
Exactly, yeah.
of course. Okay, I understand now. Okay.
Thanks.
Yeah,
that is why I was saying it will be
returned by the routing, right?
You don't have to decide which is going
to come first, right?
The routing is going to tell you here,
Yeah.
if you go see the list, the routing,
it gives you the rank, right?
Sequence one, LTL, right?
In some list, it could be TL.
TL is the number one, TL is #2,
and last would be LTL.
So it is determined by the routing itself.
You don't have to determine anything.
If the list starts with LTL and what you
are adding is an LTL equipment,
you put it bottom of that LTL list.
That's all it is saying.
Makes sense.
Okay.
Yep.
Okay, yeah, I'll go to the story again.
Right,
and add carrier to the list at the end of
the set of carriers for that equipment.
Manually,
manual pickup and delivery entry.
We did see that.
pickup and delivery entry when it should
happen, right?
A dialog box get used to a user to fill
in the date,
look at the manual pickup and delivery
entry.
So it should force the user to pick up a..
.
to enter a pickup date and a delivery
date if the routing was not able to
calculate it.
Right?
And there should be a validation message
if the delivery date and time, say,
if the user is entering the pickup date
and delivery date,
and if they enter a delivery date which
is equivalent to that of a pickup date or
earlier than a pickup date,
it should give a message saying delivery
date and time must be.
later than the pickup date.
You cannot have a pickup which is 727
when you have a pickup, sorry,
you cannot have a delivery at 727 when
you have a pickup at 728. Make sense?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
That is what it is giving this message.
The delivery date and time must be later
than the pickup date and time.
So when the user enters the pickup date
and delivery date,
it should do this validation as well.
If the entry is wrong,
it should throw out this message,
validation message to the user saying,
hey, you need to correct the date.
the pickup date and delivery date doesn't
sound, looks correct, okay,
do some action.
And it should give a button saying that
okay and cancel,
and okay is continue processing,
and okay should be enabled only when this
validation message is gone, right?
When they have corrected that the
delivery date is greater than the pickup
date.
OK, makes sense.
Yeah.
Okay.
OK,
rating processing only in case of routing
failure.
In case of rating failure,
when the rating,
say in case of the rating failure,
I will give you the message,
exact message that needs to be displayed.
It needs to tell saying that, hey,
I did try to call the rating,
but the rating failed, right?
You are not able to rate it.
And then it should say OK button.
So that okay to proceed so that the user
is aware about this message, right? Okay.
Okay,
next is the duplicate carrier validation.
We did see that the duplicate carrier,
right? When you add the carrier again,
it should say that the carrier already
exists in the list.
If I try to process this CAC again,
it should say the carrier and the
equipment combination already in the list,
right? So it should do that.
So that is what the duplicate carrier
validation.
So the carrier and the equipment
combination,
CAC and the equipment already in the list,
and the button should be okay.
So when they click on okay,
then it should stay in that screen.
Okay, the carrier insertion logic,
that is what we covered here.
Right?
The user should be able to add a carrier
and an equipment. And once they add it,
it should do the same steps as process
the SCAC because both are same.
Either they can process the SCAC from the
drop carrier list or from the process CAC
list,
or they can add a carrier and process it.
Right, when a drop carrier, sorry,
drop carrier is successfully processed
and moved to the tender list,
the carrier shall be inserted at the
bottom of the.
Matching equipment, one second.
If no marriage equipment exists,
the carrier shall be inserted into this
one.
The rank shall be calculated route rank
logic. Okay, this is a route rank logic.
It is not about this one, right?
This is not about this.
This is a route rank logic.
How to do the route rank?
If adding for the dropped carrier list,
use the route rank from the drop carrier
list. So what it...
tries to say is.
If you have a route rank,
should have a route rank somewhere, right?
If it has a route rank.
If adding from the drop carrier list,
use the route rank from the drop carrier
list.
Use the RPC ID from the drop carrier list.
Again,
all these are not important for you,
but if you are interested,
you can go read through.
I'm trying to explain it.
So if there is an RPC ID,
you're going to take the RPC ID from here
and move it there.
Right? Else,
if adding it from scratch on the tender
screen, right? This is what is this one.
If you're adding it from here,
you will not have the routing route rank
list, and you will not have the RPC ID,
right?
Adding from scratch from the tender
screen, I have to write the story,
leave the route rank empty and leave the
RPC ID empty.
Okay.
So far kind of okay.
Did you understand high level what it is?
Yeah.
Okay.
Do we still have details there?
Because I have some questions.
Yeah, few more details.
I'll just tell you once,
Okay.
once this is added, right?
Once the carrier is added,
because the user is going to work
somewhere here in the drop carrier list,
the focus should be changed to the screen,
right,
to the list to tell the user that your
carrier has been added.
So that is what this particular
information says, focus management, right?
So focus shall automatically move from
the drop.
carrier section to the tender list,
the newly added carrier shall remain
visible.
Right.
Okay,
so this is our audit logs related and
processing failure.
If the carrier cannot be processed
because of a system error,
it should tell the message,
should pop out a message to the user
saying that the drop carrier could not be
processed. If the issue persists,
please contact your system administrator.
Right? Yeah, that's it.
Go in the Manuela.
Okay.
So I have a confusion here about
tendering inside shipments.
Mhm.
And there is new overflow load board.
Mhm.
HiTech.
Your main in Odyssey one is the same
thing.
Yeah.
I need to understand the different.
It is not the same thing.
I said.
Really?
Yeah, see,
I'll tell you what is the difference.
Bye.
Here, you will have a rate, right?
You are sending this information as to
the carrier and say that, hey,
I have your rate, I have your contract,
can you accept it?
All that you are asking is,
can you accept it?
Or are you going to decline it?
That's the only message you are asking
Yeah.
the carrier, right? In the overflow board,
you're actually starting a bid.
That means you are requesting a quote.
Yeah. Sorry,
my question was not well-framed.
Let's forget about overflow.
I know what that overflow is different.
Yeah.
What I need to understand, load work.
What is the difference with that? Yeah.
Lordboard.
Yes.
Because in load work,
TMS,
we have the same thing where you can
retender and ask for the same thing that
we are doing here, for example,
ranking and all of that.
Yeah.
Exactly.
It is to assign or reassign,
or they or the planner can do changes on
top of existing tenders and all of that.
I need to understand.
Exactly. The difference I'll tell you.
Okay,
the difference between load board and
this tender page, the difference is...
Load board is internal carriers only,
so it is Odyssey owned carriers.
Okay.
Right, so, but they are in, say,
in this case, say, for example,
CTNS is one of the Odyssey carrier.
Right,
it is a generic name given to the carrier,
but you don't know which exact carrier is
going to pick up. Say, for example,
the CTNS group might have contract with
ODFL.
Within that load board,
instead of showing CTNS,
it will be showing ODFL.
But what we are telling them from here is
we are tendering it to our group company
CTNS. They will find a carrier for us,
which could be a better margin.
Right?
Once they tell us saying who that carrier
is,
we will plug that carrier here in the
list and tender to them.
Makes sense.
Could you repeat the last part again,
please?
Okay.
CTNS,
there are like load board is nothing but.
Odyssey owned load board, so it means.
Her.
No, is controlled by Odyssey, right?
It is a similar set of information where
Yeah.
the, you know,
in list of they may manage a list of
carriers for with whom they have a
contract, but...
Yeah, this what if he carriers, right?
Yeah, yeah, we don't want immediately,
say, if you have, say,
let's say CTNS Saya, CTNS ODFL, right?
It could be a long list.
We don't want to create that long list.
What they are doing is they are creating
a generic name for the...
as a carrier, this is a group, right?
For that group,
they are creating a carrier name and
posting this information in the load
board.
Right,
once they post this information in the
load board.
The load board is going to take that
information and tender it to a carrier.
Mhm.
Right, and they will tell, hey,
I tended it to a carrier,
ODFL CTNS has accepted it.
Right,
so they will pass that information back
to the tender.
What they what we will do is we will take
that information,
plug the actual carrier name,
and then again tender to that carrier.
See, I'm just telling what I know.
I don't know exactly how they do.
Is that like directly they would give a
carrier name or they would tender and
give a carrier name? I don't know,
but that is the ideal process, right?
They would either supply a carrier name
instead of CTNS,
it'll come back as saying CTNS, Sanya,
or it'll just come as Sanya, some other.
with some other, you know,
maybe like Sanya, right?
If it comes back as Sanya,
you will add that Sanya and then you will
tender to that carrier.
Instead of, it's like, imagine someone,
right?
Okay.
You're calling Odyssey Division and
asking for carrier.
They provide you a carrier,
and what do you do?
You go and add that carrier to the list
here, correct?
You add that carrier to the list and then
you quote and rate it.
Mhm.
So instead of doing it manually,
it is being done by system.
That's all that is happening.
Okay.
Makes sense.
Okay, I mean...
A little bit.
Yeah.
My perspective, yeah,
because from my perspective,
tendering inside shipments is only
different from load board, because...
in chipments,
you are targeting external carriers,
right? Instead of internal carriers.
That is my view.
Yeah.
Is I am correct or is more complicated
than that?
It is a little more complicated.
What you're saying is correct. CTNS,
that's why I said CTNS,
he said group company, right?
Whom they are going to find a carrier,
you don't know.
It could be like same ODFL,
but their contract is different.
Yeah.
Right,
I'm just saying it could be ODFL or it
could be a different carrier from any of
this list.
They might have additional carrier to
this on top of this list.
Right,
you don't know what that carrier is,
right? But once they supply that carrier,
you're going to add that carrier and
tender to that carrier.
That is why I said,
instead of user going and manually adding,
it is CTNS group is communicating via
systems saying that you tender to this
carrier. It's like someone telling you.
from CTNS that go and tender to this
carrier.
I know this carrier will accept on behalf
of us, right? So what you do is,
once you get that response,
you will mark that carrier and put it
Yeah.
inside the list and tender to that
carrier. That's all is happening.
But it sounds a little more complicated.
There could be some other logic,
but this is the logic behind that.
Mhm.
So, CTNS can have all the contracts,
right? So,
you are doing a contract on behalf of
them,
Exactly.
like you're doing a contract with CTNS.
Okay, I'm just thinking UI-wise, how to,
you know, UX-wise, how to resolve this,
because if...
They look so similar.
And tender is.
But you're not going to work on,
you're not going to work on load board,
right?
You're going to get that information from
load board and plug that carrier, right?
So you're not like changing between load
board and tender screen here.
You're just getting that information and
adding the carrier to this list.
You're passing this carrier to the load
board.
but you are not visually in any UI sense
going to work on load board.
You are not working on load board at all.
You are passing that information and
getting a response. And that response,
you are displaying it.
So the response is part of the shipments,
right? The tender shipments.
The response that is happening from the
load board.
Yeah, for each.
Yeah, correct. From the load board,
but you're not seeing it.
It is just like imagine customer ERP,
right? We are sending some information.
Hang on.
You're getting an order from customer.
You're not seeing the screen.
All that you see is they passed in this
message.
right? It's just the same way.
They are going to send you a message.
Uh-uh.
All that you're going to see is that a
message has come.
And what is that message? It is a carrier,
right? And you plug that carrier in,
and then you show that carrier,
but the details are going to be just the
same.
Whatever information came back is going
to be filled up, filled in here.
And then what do you do in Loadboard?
Other type of details, right?
Because there is some manual work to do
in Loadboard as well.
Like what?
Like tendering as well.
That is why it's complicated.
You can do tendering.
See,
you're not going to you're not going to
work on load board.
That is why I'm again and again saying
you're going to work on only the screen.
right?
Load board is just giving you a SCAC and
I know.
an equipment. Imagine that way, right?
It is going to give you,
instead of user entering here,
the load board, you are going to,
system-wise,
you are calling the CTNS system and
asking for this particular shipment,
which carrier and equipment do you
recommend?
Right?
It is passing you some carrier and
Yeah.
equipment.
There could be other information.
Mhm.
I'm trying to keep it as simple as
possible. Right?
You insert that and you will have a date,
pickup date,
delivery date all along with it.
You would get a rate and then you tender
to that carrier.
Because you need an acceptance from them.
Mm.
because they just provided you a carrier,
it doesn't mean that they have accepted
it.
It is like they're telling you,
find out with this carrier, right?
Of course.
Find out with this carrier.
Mostly he will accept it,
something like that.
No, I am just saying I need to,
like Kathleen is requiring to create a
load board UI, Kathleen and Irina.
Load board plus overflow UI.
Yeah, I am not sure about that.
That is why it was the meeting before.
So you can clarify some stuff that we
Ah.
have.
So that is why I am preoccupied here.
My understanding is you don't have to do
the load board.
You have to do the overflow,
but I don't know whether you would have
to do the load board.
Load board is already another system.
You need to communicate to that system,
but I don't think you need to interact
with.
You need to create a screen for load
Mm.
board itself.
Load board is a different system like.
That is my understanding, right?
I might be wrong,
but that is my understanding so far
because I don't see load board here.
Right in TMS, I don't see load board,
yeah.
Yeah, of course.
That is why I am not sure why they are
saying you need to create a screen for
load board. Maybe they are saying,
you know,
communicating while communicating to the
load board,
you need to show the user some
information and then pass it like some.
I don't know.
Is that the requirement or definitely
seeing a load board in your screen?
in the tender screen is not something
that I am thinking is correct.
Mm.
Because.
It could be like, say for example,
like this, right?
If you are having this carrier,
none of this carrier is there,
Yeah, I know.
you go to overflow carrier,
it is going to give you a list of
carriers.
So it doesn't mean that this is the
overflow system, right?
It is giving you a set of carriers and
you're asking them, okay,
add these carriers to the list.
it is going to add.
It could be something similar, right?
When you are creating,
it is preparing a list and telling you,
okay,
I'm going to send this message to load
board, right? This is all these details.
Are you okay to send it?
So if you say send, it sends that, right?
Is it something like that they are asking?
Mm.
I don't know.
It is one of the parts,
it is exactly the same thing.
Okay.
All of that is going to be there.
It's not part of shipments,
it's going to be as like a different
domain.
Ah, okay.
completely. Yeah,
so that is why I was asking.
Okay, okay.
If it's the same thing,
probably could be everything tender
related there,
then we have to figure out what's
valuable for users that go to shipments
to do in tender, right?
Instead of every single detail,
we can put that in.
The other domain, and...
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah,
I'm not sure about what is that load
board, right?
My understanding is load board is like,
like instead of sending to this carrier,
it's just like sending to this carrier,
you're sending it to another system,
that's it.
That's all I thought, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, we will figure it out.
Yeah, yeah, it is complex, right?
That this they built it over twenty-five
S.
years, so there's a lot of logic in it.
Yeah, it's very complex.
Yeah.
It's very complex,
and it's all over the place, so...
Yeah.
OK, Janardhana,
we should have more sessions about this.
Which one? This or load board?
The.
No, no, this of course load board as well,
but that is different topic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no problem.
Okay.
This is this is screen in TMS is too much,
is too much click and everything is in.
Some mixing, well, it's yeah.
We'll see,
that's why we are trying to do our best,
right? We have to keep,
there's a lot of information we are
trying to keep most relevant information.
If there is some information that is like
not that much relevant to the user,
we are trying to put it in a different
tab and keep it and then get their
feedback over a period of time and
eliminate those ones which are not
required.
Right, so that will happen over time.
But the first day itself,
we eliminate so many things,
they would start asking, hey,
what happened to this one, that one?
And it will be a lot of work for us,
right?
So that's why we are trying to keep all
the details that are there in TMS to like
95, 96% and.
then if we feel that those are not that
critical or important to a user to make a
decision,
we are moving it to different tabs.
Okay.
Right. Okay. Okay.
Maybe you can start the design and then,
you know, as you get along, proceed.
We can connect and we can see how it goes.
I think that's a great idea.
Yeah.
I understand it better.
Yeah,
as you start working on reading the
stories, right,
you will get different thoughts and ideas
or probably some clarification we can
connect them.
Okay.
Okay, thank you. Yeah, bye.
Okay, thank you guys.
Um, Janardhana,
could you provide me access to the
Yeah.
transcript of this one, please?
Oh yeah, I'll do that. Yeah.
Thank you. Bye bye.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.